<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <PRFHelp>Help</PRFHelp>
  <PRFHelpDesc>View help for this item.</PRFHelpDesc>
  <PRFViewOrdo>Ordo Historia: {0}</PRFViewOrdo>
  <PRF_DeepQuarry_HelpText>The deep quarry is used for extraction of random mineral resources from underground. It functions like a colonist miner would - it randomly selects a rock or compacted resource (Granite, compacted steel) according to commonality and returns its mined products. Hence, rock chunks are the most common products of deep quarries, followed by the various commonalities of other resources.</PRF_DeepQuarry_HelpText>
  <Shearer_HelpText>Animal harvesters automatically harvest animals when they come near the vicinity of the building. Store food at those stations to coerce animals to come to the stations so they can be harvested.</Shearer_HelpText>
  <Milker_HelpText>Animal harvesters automatically harvest animals when they come near the vicinity of the building. Store food at those stations to coerce animals to come to the stations so they can be harvested.</Milker_HelpText>
  <GenericAnimalHarvester_HelpText>Animal harvesters automatically harvest animals when they come near the vicinity of the building. Store food at those stations to coerce animals to come to the stations so they can be harvested.</GenericAnimalHarvester_HelpText>
  <PaperclipFactory_HelpText>The paperclip factory doesn't just take in steel - it can make paperclips from any item by manipulating its subatomic structure. The number of paperclips produced is equivalent to 1/4 of the combined mass of the ingredients.</PaperclipFactory_HelpText>
  <PaperclipFactory_OrdoText>The paperclip shape was unique in that it gives matter a 0.006% lower zero-point energy, which ultimately gives it lower resistance to atomic disassembly. On glitterworlds, materials for molecular reassembly are often stored in raw subatomic components, which do not need to be broken down, but because maintenance requires extreme amounts of power, paperclips are still used in some consumer-grade item reconstructors.</PaperclipFactory_OrdoText>
</LanguageData>